fastcollab.com 2019-06-11

# FastCollab | Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how FastCollab uses and protects any information that you give FastCollab when you use this website. FastCollab is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, and then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. FastCollab may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically. 

###  What we collect

We may collect the following information 

  * Name
  * Contact information including email address
  * Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
  * Billing and Credit Card information when you purchase something. This information is not stored
  * Computer hardware and software information which includes your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This is used for the operation of service, to maintain and improve the quality of the service and for general statistics

We collect this personally identifiable information from you when you set up a free account with FastCollab . With registration, you will be allowed to browse certain sections of the site. For using the service, registration is required.. We do use your contact information to send you offers based on your previous orders and your interests. 

###  What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons 

  * Internal record keeping
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests

FastCollab will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on FastCollab or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of FastCollab; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of FastCollab, or the public

###  Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

###  Data Security

All the applicant's details and data uploaded by a user in the system totally belongs to the user. In no condition, FastCollab will re-distribute or share this data with any third party organisation. Also, FastCollab will not use this database for any of its own business interests in future. 

###  Cookies

A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a web server on your web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. FastCollab places both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer's hard drive. FastCollab's cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information except your user id.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

###  Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

###  Choice/Opt-Out

FastCollab provides all users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non- essential (promotional, marketing-related) communications from us on behalf of our partners, and from us in general, after setting up an account.

###  Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below 

FastCollab Systems Private Limited  
Catalyst Building, T-Hub  
IIIT Gachibowli, Hyderabad  
Telangana 500036, India  
+91 40 4265 6565  
Email: customercare@fastcollab.com
